[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "der Rabe",
		"extra": "die Raben",
		"answer": ["holló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "geschickte",
		"extra": "geschickten",
		"answer": ["elküld"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "sieh mich an",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Nézz rám!"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "das war",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ez volt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "die Aufgabe",
		"extra": "die Aufgaben",
		"answer": ["feladat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "einzeige",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyetlen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "müssen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kell"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "zurük",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vissza"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "die mauer",
		"extra": "die mauern",
		"answer": ["fal"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "wiss",
		"extra": "wissen",
		"answer": ["tud"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "draußen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kívül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "aber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["de"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "schaffen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["teremt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "wird",
		"extra": "werden",
		"answer": ["válik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "sonst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["másképp"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 16,
		"question": "jeder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mindenki"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "tot",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["halott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 18,
		"question": "jemals",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valaha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 19,
		"question": "nur",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 20,
		"question": "immer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mindig"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 21,
		"question": "viel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 22,
		"question": "schon",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["már"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 23,
		"question": "noch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["még"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 24,
		"question": "fertig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kész"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 25,
		"question": "zu",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tól"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 26,
		"question": "dran",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["turn"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 27,
		"question": "allaine",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyedül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 28,
		"question": "vielleicht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["talán"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 29,
		"question": "zusammen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["együtt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 30,
		"question": "wieder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["újra"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 31,
		"question": "die Tür",
		"extra": "die Türen",
		"answer": ["ajtó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 32,
		"question": "tief",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mély"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 33,
		"question": "öffne",
		"extra": "öffnen",
		"answer": ["nyit"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 34,
		"question": "sauber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tiszta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 35,
		"question": "der Zaun",
		"extra": "die Zäune",
		"answer": ["kerítés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 36,
		"question": "das Fenster",
		"extra": "die Fenster",
		"answer": ["ablak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 37,
		"question": "jedes",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mindegyik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 38,
		"question": "die Wand",
		"extra": "die Wände",
		"answer": ["fal"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 39,
		"question": "die Decke",
		"extra": "die Decken",
		"answer": ["takaró"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 40,
		"question": "der Keller",
		"extra": "die Keller",
		"answer": ["pince"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 41,
		"question": "die Treppe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a lépcső"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 42,
		"question": "der Balkon",
		"extra": "die Balkone",
		"answer": ["erkély"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 43,
		"question": "die Küche",
		"extra": "die Küchen",
		"answer": ["konyha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 44,
		"question": "der schlüssel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kulcs"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 45,
		"question": "die Wohnung",
		"extra": "die Wohnungen",
		"answer": ["lakás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 46,
		"question": "das Dach",
		"extra": "die Dächer",
		"answer": ["tető"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 47,
		"question": "die Möbel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bútor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 48,
		"question": "der Stuhl",
		"extra": "die Stühle",
		"answer": ["szék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 49,
		"question": "schwach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyenge"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 50,
		"question": "der Tisch",
		"extra": "die Tische",
		"answer": ["asztal"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 51,
		"question": "traurig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szomorú"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 52,
		"question": "das Wohnzimmer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nappali"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 53,
		"question": "müde",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fáradt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 54,
		"question": "lustig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vicces"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 55,
		"question": "der Teppich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szőnyeg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 56,
		"question": "weit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["messze"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 57,
		"question": "schmutzig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["koszos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 58,
		"question": "das bett",
		"extra": "die Betten",
		"answer": ["ágy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 59,
		"question": "das Schlafzimmer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hálószoba"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 60,
		"question": "heute",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 61,
		"question": "jezt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["most"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 62,
		"question": "nie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["soha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 63,
		"question": "erster",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["első"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 64,
		"question": "zweite",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["második"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 65,
		"question": "dritte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["harmadik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 66,
		"question": "der Riese",
		"extra": "die Riesen",
		"answer": ["óriás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 67,
		"question": "der Schnee",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 68,
		"question": "sohin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["így"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 69,
		"question": "starre",
		"extra": "starren",
		"answer": ["bámul"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 70,
		"question": "schüchtern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["félénk"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 71,
		"question": "mehr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["több"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 72,
		"question": "wütend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mérges"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 73,
		"question": "schlage",
		"extra": "schlagen",
		"answer": ["üt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 74,
		"question": "der Baden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["padló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 75,
		"question": "wie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hogyan", "ahogyan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 76,
		"question": "der Nagel",
		"extra": "die Nagel",
		"answer": ["köröm"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 77,
		"question": "die Krähe",
		"extra": "die Krähen",
		"answer": ["varjú"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 78,
		"question": "drüben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 79,
		"question": "falsche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rossz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 80,
		"question": "Farbe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ruha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 81,
		"question": "verschwinde",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["menj innen!"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 82,
		"question": "herz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szív"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 83,
		"question": "wollen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["akar"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 84,
		"question": "wenn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 85,
		"question": "dann",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["azután"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 86,
		"question": "steht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["áll"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 87,
		"question": "mir",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nekem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 88,
		"question": "verhauen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["megver"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 89,
		"question": "frech",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rossz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 90,
		"question": "passiere",
		"extra": "passieren",
		"answer": ["történik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 91,
		"question": "wurden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["voltak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 92,
		"question": "manche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["néhány"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 93,
		"question": "guck",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["néz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 94,
		"question": "rieche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szag"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 95,
		"question": "verhören",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kihallgat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 96,
		"question": "soll",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kellene"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 97,
		"question": "nützen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["haszon"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 98,
		"question": "sagte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mondott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 99,
		"question": "durchs",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["keresztül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 100,
		"question": "bohr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fúró"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 101,
		"question": "viele",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 102,
		"question": "versuche",
		"extra": "versuchen",
		"answer": ["próbál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 103,
		"question": "liege",
		"extra": "liegen",
		"answer": ["fekszik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 1, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 104,
		"question": "euer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["your"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 105,
		"question": "jedem",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["minden egyes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 106,
		"question": "furz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fing"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 107,
		"question": "jenzeits",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["túl"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 108,
		"question": "präsent",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ajándék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 109,
		"question": "herr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["úr"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 110,
		"question": "der Knochen",
		"extra": "die Knochen",
		"answer": ["csont"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 111,
		"question": "scheint",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["úgy tűnik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 112,
		"question": "deshalb",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ezért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 113,
		"question": "verdamten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rohadt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 114,
		"question": "kaum zu glauben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nehéz elhinni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 115,
		"question": "froh",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["boldog"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 116,
		"question": "feind",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ellenség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 117,
		"question": "als",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["amikor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 118,
		"question": "ganze",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egész"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 119,
		"question": "suche",
		"extra": "suchen",
		"answer": ["keres"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 120,
		"question": "etwas",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valami"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 121,
		"question": "einmal",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyszer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 122,
		"question": "mal",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["alkalom"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 123,
		"question": "der Held",
		"extra": "die Helden",
		"answer": ["hős"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 124,
		"question": "die Frage",
		"extra": "die Fragen",
		"answer": ["kérdés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 125,
		"question": "letzes",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["utolsó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 126,
		"question": "warum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 127,
		"question": "wieso",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 128,
		"question": "das Kino",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mozi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 129,
		"question": "ins",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["to the"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 130,
		"question": "genau",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["helyes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 131,
		"question": "kauf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vesz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 132,
		"question": "auch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["also"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 133,
		"question": "genug",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elég"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 134,
		"question": "nehmen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elvisz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 135,
		"question": "Samstagabend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szombat este"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 136,
		"question": "konzertkarten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["koncertjegy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 137,
		"question": "die schwestern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sisters"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 138,
		"question": "plane",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["terv"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 139,
		"question": "Wochenende",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hétvége"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 140,
		"question": "beim",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["at the"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 141,
		"question": "mache",
		"extra": "machen",
		"answer": ["csinál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 142,
		"question": "die Gebäude",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["épület"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 143,
		"question": "die Ecke",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sarok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 144,
		"question": "mag",
		"extra": "mögen",
		"answer": ["szeret"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 145,
		"question": "die Schul",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["iskola"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 146,
		"question": "der Bahnhof",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vasútállomás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 147,
		"question": "die Bibliothek",
		"extra": "die Bibliotheken",
		"answer": ["könyvtár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 148,
		"question": "der Schloss",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kastély"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 149,
		"question": "der Burg",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 150,
		"question": "das Restaurant",
		"extra": "die Restaurants",
		"answer": ["étterem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 151,
		"question": "die Brücke",
		"extra": "die Brücken",
		"answer": ["híd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 152,
		"question": "das Dorf",
		"extra": "die Dörfe",
		"answer": ["falu"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 153,
		"question": "die Stadt",
		"extra": "die Städte",
		"answer": ["város"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 154,
		"question": "euch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["titeket"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 155,
		"question": "verstehe",
		"extra": "verstehen",
		"answer": ["megért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 156,
		"question": "dich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["téged"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 157,
		"question": "sie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["téged"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 158,
		"question": "uns",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["minket"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 159,
		"question": "mich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["engem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 160,
		"question": "ihn, ihr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["őt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 161,
		"question": "unseren",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["our"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 162,
		"question": "mein",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["my"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 163,
		"question": "deine",
		"extra": "eure",
		"answer": ["your"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 164,
		"question": "seine",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["its"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 165,
		"question": "andere",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["másik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 166,
		"question": "aus",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ki"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 167,
		"question": "Geschlect",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 168,
		"question": "wichtig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fontos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 169,
		"question": "Gast",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vendég"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 170,
		"question": "gegner",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ellenfél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 171,
		"question": "mitglied",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tag"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 172,
		"question": "nachbarn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szomszéd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 173,
		"question": "der Anfänger",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kezdő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 174,
		"question": "das Obst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyümölcs"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 175,
		"question": "trage",
		"extra": "tragen",
		"answer": ["visz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 176,
		"question": "besucher",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["látogató"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 177,
		"question": "entweder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["either"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 178,
		"question": "oder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vagy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 179,
		"question": "leise",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csendes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 180,
		"question": "denn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mert"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 181,
		"question": "doch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["de"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 182,
		"question": "aber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["de"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 183,
		"question": "der Knopf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gomb"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 184,
		"question": "weil",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 185,
		"question": "wenn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ha", "amikor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 186,
		"question": "dass",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["azt hogy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 187,
		"question": "auch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szintén"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 188,
		"question": "da",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 189,
		"question": "obwohl",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mégis"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 190,
		"question": "solange",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["amíg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 191,
		"question": "gesund",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egészséges"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 192,
		"question": "da",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mivel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 193,
		"question": "sobald",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["amint"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 194,
		"question": "sondern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hanem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 195,
		"question": "der Bruder",
		"extra": "die Brüder",
		"answer": ["brother"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 196,
		"question": "die Tochter",
		"extra": "die Töchter",
		"answer": ["daughter"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 197,
		"question": "der Sohn",
		"extra": "die Söhne",
		"answer": ["son"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 198,
		"question": "die Schwester",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sister"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 199,
		"question": "die Eltern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a szülők"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 200,
		"question": "nur",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyetlen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 201,
		"question": "Geschwister",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["testvér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 202,
		"question": "Beziehung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kapcsolat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 203,
		"question": "Großvater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nagyapa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 204,
		"question": "Enkel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["unoka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 205,
		"question": "das Ei",
		"extra": "die Eier",
		"answer": ["tojás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 206,
		"question": "das Fleisch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hús"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 207,
		"question": "schmeckt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tastes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 208,
		"question": "der Käse",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sajt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 209,
		"question": "das Gemüse",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["zöldség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 210,
		"question": "wann",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mikor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 211,
		"question": "wo",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hol"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 212,
		"question": "woher",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["honnan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 213,
		"question": "wohin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hová"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 214,
		"question": "wer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ki"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 215,
		"question": "worüber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miről"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 216,
		"question": "wenn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 217,
		"question": "wofür",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 218,
		"question": "wieso",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 219,
		"question": "warum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["miért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 220,
		"question": "womit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mivel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 221,
		"question": "welche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["melyik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 222,
		"question": "wie viel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mennyi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 223,
		"question": "wie bitte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["come again"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 224,
		"question": "aus wie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mint(like)"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 225,
		"question": "wie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hogyan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 226,
		"question": "das Kleid",
		"extra": "Kleider",
		"answer": ["ruha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 227,
		"question": "der Hut",
		"extra": "Hüte",
		"answer": ["sapka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 228,
		"question": "der Mantel",
		"extra": "Mäntel",
		"answer": ["kabát"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 229,
		"question": "die Hose",
		"extra": "Hosen",
		"answer": ["nadrág"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 230,
		"question": "das Hemd",
		"extra": "Hemden",
		"answer": ["ing"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 231,
		"question": "passen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["illik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 232,
		"question": "der Schmuck",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["éksszer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 233,
		"question": "die Tasche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a táska"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 234,
		"question": "fleck",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["folt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 235,
		"question": "der Ring",
		"extra": "Ringe",
		"answer": ["gyűrű"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 236,
		"question": "die Erde",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a Föld"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 237,
		"question": "der Wind",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 238,
		"question": "die Natur",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["természet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 239,
		"question": "der baum",
		"extra": "Bäume",
		"answer": ["fa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 240,
		"question": "der Mond",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a Hold"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 241,
		"question": "die Luft",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["levegő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 242,
		"question": "das Fauer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tűz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 243,
		"question": "die Blume",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["virág"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 244,
		"question": "das Meer",
		"extra": "Meere",
		"answer": ["tenger"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 245,
		"question": "der Ozean",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["óceán"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 246,
		"question": "der Himmel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["az ég"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 247,
		"question": "falle",
		"extra": "fallen",
		"answer": ["esik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 248,
		"question": "die Sonne",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a Nap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 249,
		"question": "der Stern",
		"extra": "Sterne",
		"answer": ["csillag"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 250,
		"question": "lebe",
		"extra": "leben",
		"answer": ["él"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 251,
		"question": "entlang",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["along"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 252,
		"question": "um",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["körbe", "around"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 253,
		"question": "durch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["keresztül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 254,
		"question": "ohne",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nélkül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 255,
		"question": "für",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nak", "nek"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 256,
		"question": "gegen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ellen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 257,
		"question": "nummer",
		"extra": "nummern",
		"answer": ["szám"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 258,
		"question": "eins",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 259,
		"question": "zwei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kettő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 260,
		"question": "drei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["három"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 261,
		"question": "vier",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["négy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 262,
		"question": "fünf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["öt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 263,
		"question": "sechs",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 264,
		"question": "sieben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hétvége"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 265,
		"question": "acht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyolc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 266,
		"question": "neun",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kilenc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 1, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 267,
		"question": "zehn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tíz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 268,
		"question": "elf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tizenegy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 269,
		"question": "zwölf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tizenkettő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 270,
		"question": "dreizehn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tizenhárom"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 271,
		"question": "vierzehn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tizennégy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 272,
		"question": "zwanzig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["húsz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 273,
		"question": "dreißig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["harminc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 274,
		"question": "hundert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["száz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 275,
		"question": "einhundertfünfundzwanzig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["százhuszonöt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 276,
		"question": "tausend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ezer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 277,
		"question": "es gibt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["there is", "van"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 278,
		"question": "der Honig",
		"extra": "Honige",
		"answer": ["méz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 279,
		"question": "die Marmalade",
		"extra": "Marmaladen",
		"answer": ["lekvár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 280,
		"question": "frühstückt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["reggeli"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 281,
		"question": "die nuss",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dió"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 282,
		"question": "Pilz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gomba"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 283,
		"question": "Huhn, Hähnchen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csirke"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 284,
		"question": "das Rezept",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["recept"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 285,
		"question": "Mittagessen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ebéd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 286,
		"question": "Getränke",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ital"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 287,
		"question": "bohnen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["babok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 288,
		"question": "kocht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["süt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 289,
		"question": "sauer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["savanyú"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 290,
		"question": "Speisekarte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["menü"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 291,
		"question": "Zwiebel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hagyma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 292,
		"question": "Knoblauch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fokhagyma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 293,
		"question": "Senf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mustár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 294,
		"question": "Vorspeise",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["előétel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 295,
		"question": "scharf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csipős étel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 296,
		"question": "Hauptgericht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["főétel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 297,
		"question": "Löffel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kanál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 298,
		"question": "Gabel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["villa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 299,
		"question": "Messer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 300,
		"question": "Abendessen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vacsora"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 301,
		"question": "Kuchen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["torta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 302,
		"question": "Nachtisch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["desszert"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 303,
		"question": "kosten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kerül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 304,
		"question": "Preis",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 305,
		"question": "Geld",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["pénz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 306,
		"question": "kaufs",
		"extra": "kaufen",
		"answer": ["vesz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 307,
		"question": "wieder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["újra"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 308,
		"question": "nur",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["éppen", "only"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 309,
		"question": "reich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gazdag"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 310,
		"question": "Zeug",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dolog"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 311,
		"question": "überweise",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["átruházni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 312,
		"question": "gewinnst",
		"extra": "gewinnen",
		"answer": ["nyer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 313,
		"question": "besitzt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["birtokol"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 1, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 314,
		"question": "ein paar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egy pár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 315,
		"question": "Tante",
		"extra": "Tanten",
		"answer": ["nagynény"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 316,
		"question": "Neffe",
		"extra": "Neffen",
		"answer": ["unokaöccs"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 317,
		"question": "verwandten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rokon"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 318,
		"question": "Onkel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nagybácsi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 319,
		"question": "ruhig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyugodt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 320,
		"question": "Nichte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["unokahúg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 321,
		"question": "Zwilling",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ikertestvér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 322,
		"question": "Urgroßmutter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dédanya"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 323,
		"question": "Ueenkel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dédunoka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 324,
		"question": "Halbbruder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["féltestvér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 325,
		"question": "schwanger",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["terhes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 326,
		"question": "Hochzeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["esküvő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 327,
		"question": "beiden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mindkét"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 328,
		"question": "verheiratet",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["házasok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 329,
		"question": "der Körper",
		"extra": "Körper",
		"answer": ["test"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 330,
		"question": "die Haare",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["haj"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 331,
		"question": "das Ohr",
		"extra": "Ohren",
		"answer": ["fül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 332,
		"question": "das Auge",
		"extra": "Augen",
		"answer": ["szem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 333,
		"question": "der Kopf",
		"extra": "Köpfe",
		"answer": ["fej"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 334,
		"question": "die Nase",
		"extra": "Nasen",
		"answer": ["orr"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 335,
		"question": "der Arm",
		"extra": "Arme",
		"answer": ["kar"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 336,
		"question": "der Zahn",
		"extra": "Zähne",
		"answer": ["fog"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 337,
		"question": "der Hals",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 338,
		"question": "der Mund",
		"extra": "Münder",
		"answer": ["száj"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 339,
		"question": "drückst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyom"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 340,
		"question": "der Finger",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ujj"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 341,
		"question": "die Hand",
		"extra": "Hände",
		"answer": ["kéz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 342,
		"question": "die Schulter",
		"extra": "Schultern",
		"answer": ["váll"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 343,
		"question": "die Brust",
		"extra": "Brüste",
		"answer": ["mell"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 344,
		"question": "Rücken",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hát"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 345,
		"question": "der Magen",
		"extra": "Mägen",
		"answer": ["gyomor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 1, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 346,
		"question": "das Herz",
		"extra": "Herzen",
		"answer": ["szív"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 347,
		"question": "der Fuß",
		"extra": "Füße",
		"answer": ["láb"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 348,
		"question": "Blut",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 349,
		"question": "Gesicht",
		"extra": "Gesichter",
		"answer": ["arc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 350,
		"question": "Bein",
		"extra": "Beine",
		"answer": ["láb"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 351,
		"question": "die Haut",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bőr"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 352,
		"question": "irgendwie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valahogy"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 353,
		"question": "irgendwo",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valahol"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 354,
		"question": "irgendwann",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valamikor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 355,
		"question": "irgendwas",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valami"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 356,
		"question": "irgendwer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valaki"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 357,
		"question": "Prozent",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["százalék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 358,
		"question": "Bayern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Bajorország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 359,
		"question": "Österreich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Ausztria"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 360,
		"question": "das Fahrrad",
		"extra": "Fahrräder",
		"answer": ["bicikli"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 361,
		"question": "der Zug",
		"extra": "Züge",
		"answer": ["vonat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 362,
		"question": "der Urlaub",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vakáció"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 363,
		"question": "Wien",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Bécs"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 364,
		"question": "von",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tól", "from"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 365,
		"question": "nach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ba be", "to"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 366,
		"question": "aus",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ból", "from"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 367,
		"question": "bei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nál nél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 368,
		"question": "der Pass",
		"extra": "Pässe",
		"answer": ["útlevél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 369,
		"question": "Deutschland",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Németország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 370,
		"question": "Italien",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Olaszország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 371,
		"question": "Frankreich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Franciország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 372,
		"question": "Ferien",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vakáció"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 373,
		"question": "die Reise",
		"extra": "Reisen",
		"answer": ["utazás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 374,
		"question": "das Land",
		"extra": "Länder",
		"answer": ["Ország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 375,
		"question": "zum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hoz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 376,
		"question": "Visum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["viza"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 377,
		"question": "Spanien",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Spanyolország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 378,
		"question": "der Weg",
		"extra": "Wege",
		"answer": ["út", "path"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 379,
		"question": "Sehenswürdigkeiten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["látványosság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 380,
		"question": "um",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["körül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 381,
		"question": "Flug",
		"extra": "Flüge",
		"answer": ["repülőút"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 382,
		"question": "Tourismus",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["turizmus"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 383,
		"question": "Reiseführer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["útikalauz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 384,
		"question": "der Stadtplan",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["város térkép"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 385,
		"question": "die Fahrt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["út", "drive"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 386,
		"question": "Mietwagen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["autó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 387,
		"question": "der Strecken",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["útszakasz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 388,
		"question": "die Schweiz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Svájc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 389,
		"question": "der Verkehr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["forgalom"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 390,
		"question": "Motorräder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["motorbicikli"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 391,
		"question": "der Schweizer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["svájci"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 392,
		"question": "Abentauer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kaland"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 393,
		"question": "nach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["to"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 394,
		"question": "das Boot",
		"extra": "Boote",
		"answer": ["hajó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 395,
		"question": "Großbritannien",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Nagybritannia"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 396,
		"question": "wandern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hegyet mászni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 397,
		"question": "die Bahn",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vonat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 398,
		"question": "buche",
		"extra": "buchen",
		"answer": ["foglal"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 399,
		"question": "fliegt",
		"extra": "fliegen",
		"answer": ["repül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 400,
		"question": "die Vespätung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["késés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 401,
		"question": "zur",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nak nek"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 402,
		"question": "Bushaltestelle",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["buszmegálló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 403,
		"question": "Schweden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Svédország"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 404,
		"question": "das Geschäft",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["üzlet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 405,
		"question": "Laden",
		"extra": "Läden",
		"answer": ["bolt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 406,
		"question": "der Marktplatz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["piac"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 407,
		"question": "die Bäckerei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["pékség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 408,
		"question": "einkaufen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vásárlás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 409,
		"question": "der Kunden, die Kundin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ügyfél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 410,
		"question": "verkauft",
		"extra": "verkaufen",
		"answer": ["árul"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 411,
		"question": "Tüte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szatyor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 412,
		"question": "Kasse",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kassza"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 413,
		"question": "kauft",
		"extra": "kaufen",
		"answer": ["vesz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 414,
		"question": "der Supermarkt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szupermarket"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 415,
		"question": "die Apotheke",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["patika"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 416,
		"question": "der Gutschein",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["utalvány"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 417,
		"question": "billig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["olcsó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 418,
		"question": "Sonderangebot",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["akció"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 419,
		"question": "das Einkaufszentrum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bevásárló központ"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 420,
		"question": "erste",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["első"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 421,
		"question": "zweite",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["második"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 422,
		"question": "dritte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["harmadik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 423,
		"question": "vierte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["negyedik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 424,
		"question": "fünfte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ötödik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 425,
		"question": "sechste",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hatodik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 426,
		"question": "siebte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hetedik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 427,
		"question": "achte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyolcadik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 428,
		"question": "neunte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kilencedik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 429,
		"question": "zehntel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tizedik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 430,
		"question": "der Author",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szerző"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 431,
		"question": "ähnlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hasonló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 432,
		"question": "Schüler",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["diák"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 433,
		"question": "die Farben",
		"extra": "die Farben",
		"answer": ["szín"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 434,
		"question": "grün",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["zöld"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 435,
		"question": "rot",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["piros"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 436,
		"question": "blau",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 437,
		"question": "weiß",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fehér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 438,
		"question": "schwarz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fekete"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 439,
		"question": "gelb",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sárga"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 440,
		"question": "bunt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["színes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 441,
		"question": "grau",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szürke"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 442,
		"question": "pink",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lila"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 443,
		"question": "Arzt, ärztin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["orvos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 444,
		"question": "Koch, Köchin",
		"extra": "Köche",
		"answer": ["szakács"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 445,
		"question": "Berufe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szakma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 446,
		"question": "Lehrer, Lehrerin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tanár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 447,
		"question": "Professor, Professorin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["professzor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 448,
		"question": "Mitarbeiter, Mitarbeiterin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["munkatárs"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 449,
		"question": "Arbeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["munka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 450,
		"question": "Arbeitgeber, arbeitgeberin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["munkáltató"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 451,
		"question": "der Arbeitnehmer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["munkavállaló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 452,
		"question": "der Geschäftsführer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ügyvezető igazgató"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 1, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 453,
		"question": "Partnerschaft",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["parnerség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 454,
		"question": "Händler",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kereskedő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 455,
		"question": "der Trainer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["edző"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 456,
		"question": "Chef, Chefin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["főnök"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 457,
		"question": "der Bürgermeister",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["polgármester"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 458,
		"question": "der Bauer",
		"extra": "Bauern",
		"answer": ["farmer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 459,
		"question": "der Verkaufer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["eladó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 460,
		"question": "die Bedienung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["felszolgálás", "pincér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 461,
		"question": "die Feuerwehr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tűzoltóság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 462,
		"question": "der Sand",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["homok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 463,
		"question": "die Wolle",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyapjú"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 464,
		"question": "der Stein",
		"extra": "Steine",
		"answer": ["kő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 465,
		"question": "der Beton",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["beton"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 466,
		"question": "das Plastik",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["műanyag"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 467,
		"question": "das Glas",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["üveg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 468,
		"question": "das Leder",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bőr"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 469,
		"question": "das Papier",
		"extra": "Papiere",
		"answer": ["papír"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 470,
		"question": "das Holz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 471,
		"question": "die Baumwolle",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["pamut"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 472,
		"question": "das Feuer",
		"extra": "die Feuer",
		"answer": ["tűz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 473,
		"question": "das Pappe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["karton"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 474,
		"question": "das Gold",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["arany"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 475,
		"question": "das Silber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ezüst"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 476,
		"question": "das Kupfer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["réz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 477,
		"question": "der Stahl",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["acél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 478,
		"question": "der Eisen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vas"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 479,
		"question": "das Metall",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fém"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 480,
		"question": "das Gerät",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["eszköz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 481,
		"question": "die Heizung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fűtés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 482,
		"question": "das Haushaltsgeräte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["háztartási készülék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 483,
		"question": "der Umzug",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["költözés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 484,
		"question": "der Haushalt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["háztartás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 485,
		"question": "die Reinigung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["takarítás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 486,
		"question": "die Batterie",
		"extra": "Batterien",
		"answer": ["elem", "akkumulátor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 487,
		"question": "die Zahnbürste",
		"extra": "Zahnbürsten",
		"answer": ["fogkefe"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 488,
		"question": "der Raum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szoba"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 489,
		"question": "als",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mint"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 490,
		"question": "voll",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["teli", "telt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 491,
		"question": "die Leiter",
		"extra": "Leitern",
		"answer": ["létra"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 492,
		"question": "die Zahnpasta",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fogkrém"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 493,
		"question": "leer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["üres"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 494,
		"question": "das Tor",
		"extra": "Tore",
		"answer": ["kapu"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 495,
		"question": "der Teller",
		"extra": "Teller",
		"answer": ["tányér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 496,
		"question": "die Tasse",
		"extra": "Tassen",
		"answer": ["csésze"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 497,
		"question": "die Schüssel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 498,
		"question": "der Karton",
		"extra": "Kartons",
		"answer": ["doboz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 499,
		"question": "der Rucksack",
		"extra": "Rucksäcke",
		"answer": ["hátizsák"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 500,
		"question": "der Kühlschrank",
		"extra": "Kühlschränke",
		"answer": ["hűtő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 501,
		"question": "der Toalette",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mosdó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 502,
		"question": "duscht",
		"extra": "duschen",
		"answer": ["zuhanyzik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 503,
		"question": "der Spiegel",
		"extra": "Spiegel",
		"answer": ["tükör"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 504,
		"question": "die Seife",
		"extra": "Seifen",
		"answer": ["szappan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 505,
		"question": "der Flasche",
		"extra": "Flaschen",
		"answer": ["flakon", "üveg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 506,
		"question": "das Bad",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fürdőszoba"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 507,
		"question": "die Razierer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["borotva"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 508,
		"question": "hinter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mögött"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 509,
		"question": "das Handtuch",
		"extra": "Handtücher",
		"answer": ["törölköző"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 510,
		"question": "Duschgel",
		"extra": "Duschgels",
		"answer": ["tusfürdő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 511,
		"question": "Shampoo",
		"extra": "Shampoos",
		"answer": ["sampon"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 512,
		"question": "der Dusche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["zuhanyzó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 513,
		"question": "Montag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hétfő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 514,
		"question": "Dienstag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kedd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 515,
		"question": "Mittwoch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szerda"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 516,
		"question": "Donnerstag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csütörtök"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 517,
		"question": "Freitag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["péntek"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 518,
		"question": "Samtag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szombat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 519,
		"question": "Sonntag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vasárnap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 520,
		"question": "am Tag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["naponta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 521,
		"question": "Werktage",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["munkanap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 522,
		"question": "der Woche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hét"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 523,
		"question": "Alltag",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["napi rutin"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 524,
		"question": "täglich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["naponta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 525,
		"question": "die Zukunft",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["jövő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 526,
		"question": "zwischen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["között"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 527,
		"question": "Vergangenheit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["múlt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 528,
		"question": "der Anfang",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kezdet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 529,
		"question": "das Ende",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vég"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 530,
		"question": "Endlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["végül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 531,
		"question": "bald",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hamarosan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 532,
		"question": "inzwischen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["közben"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 533,
		"question": "danach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["utána"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 534,
		"question": "spätestens",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["legkésőbb"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 535,
		"question": "wöchentlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hétvégente"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 536,
		"question": "mir",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["engem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 537,
		"question": "dir",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["téged"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 538,
		"question": "ihm",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["őt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 539,
		"question": "ihr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["őt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 540,
		"question": "uns",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["minket"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 541,
		"question": "euch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["titeket"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 542,
		"question": "ihnen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["őket", "magát", "magukat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 543,
		"question": "meinem, meiner, meinen vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["az én apámat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 544,
		"question": "deinem, deiner, deinen vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a te apádat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 545,
		"question": "seinem, seiner, seinen, ihrem, ihrer, ihren vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["az ő apját"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 546,
		"question": "unserem, unsererm unseren vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a mi apánkat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 547,
		"question": "eurem, eurer, euren vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["a ti apátokat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 548,
		"question": "ihrem, ihrer, ihren vater",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["az ő apjukat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 549,
		"question": "von",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tól", "től", "ról", "ről", "ból", "ből"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 550,
		"question": "mit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["val", "vel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 551,
		"question": "seit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mióta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 1, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 552,
		"question": "bei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nál", "nél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 553,
		"question": "nach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["után", "felé", "ba", "be", "ra", "re"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 554,
		"question": "zu",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hoz", "hez", "höz", "ra", "re", "vá", "vé", "on", "en ", "ön"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 555,
		"question": "beim",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nál", "nél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 556,
		"question": "um, ums",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["körül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 557,
		"question": "an",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["on", "en", "ön", "nál", "nél", "ra", "re"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 558,
		"question": "außer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kivéve"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 559,
		"question": "einschließlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["beleértve"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 560,
		"question": "wegen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mert", "amiért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 561,
		"question": "für",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ért", "nak", "nek"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 562,
		"question": "bis",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ig"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 563,
		"question": "aus",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ból", "ből"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 564,
		"question": "ab",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tól", "től"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 565,
		"question": "entgegen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ellen", "ellenére"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 566,
		"question": "gegenüber",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szemben"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 567,
		"question": "hinter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mögött"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 568,
		"question": "vor",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["előtt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 569,
		"question": "neben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mellett"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 570,
		"question": "unter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["alatt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 571,
		"question": "über",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fölött"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 572,
		"question": "zwischen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["között"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 573,
		"question": "Größe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["méret"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 574,
		"question": "ziemlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egészen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 575,
		"question": "die Beziehung",
		"extra": "Beziehungen",
		"answer": ["kapcsolat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 576,
		"question": "ziemlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["eléggé"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 577,
		"question": "sehr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nagyon"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 578,
		"question": "ganz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["teljesen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 579,
		"question": "normalerweise",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["alapesetben", "normálisan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 580,
		"question": "eher",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["inkább"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 581,
		"question": "gewöhnlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["általában"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 582,
		"question": "außen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kint"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 583,
		"question": "draußen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kint"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 584,
		"question": "innen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bent"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 585,
		"question": "drinnen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bent"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 586,
		"question": "da drüben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 587,
		"question": "dort drüben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 588,
		"question": "da",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 589,
		"question": "dort",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 590,
		"question": "hier",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["itt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 591,
		"question": "nebenan",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szomszédban"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 592,
		"question": "hinten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hátul"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 593,
		"question": "vorne",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elől"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 594,
		"question": "oben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fent"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 595,
		"question": "unten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lent"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 596,
		"question": "da vorne",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 597,
		"question": "überall",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mindenhol"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 598,
		"question": "die Umgebung",
		"extra": "Umgebungen",
		"answer": ["környék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 1, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 599,
		"question": "die Innerstadt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["belváros"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 600,
		"question": "die Kneipe",
		"extra": "Kneipen",
		"answer": ["bár", "kocsma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 601,
		"question": "der Platz",
		"extra": "Plätze",
		"answer": ["tér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 602,
		"question": "der Ort",
		"extra": "Orten",
		"answer": ["hely"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 603,
		"question": "der Bereich",
		"extra": "Bereiche",
		"answer": ["terület"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 604,
		"question": "die Unterkunft",
		"extra": "Unterkünfte",
		"answer": ["szállás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 605,
		"question": "wohne",
		"extra": "wohnen",
		"answer": ["lakni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 606,
		"question": "die Pension",
		"extra": "Pensionen",
		"answer": ["panzió"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 607,
		"question": "die Region",
		"extra": "Regionen",
		"answer": ["régió"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 608,
		"question": "der Grund",
		"extra": "Gründe",
		"answer": ["talaj", "ok"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 609,
		"question": "der Bezirk",
		"extra": "Bezirke",
		"answer": ["kerület"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 610,
		"question": "der Flughafen",
		"extra": "Flughäfen",
		"answer": ["reptér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 611,
		"question": "die Halle",
		"extra": "Hallen",
		"answer": ["hall"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 612,
		"question": "der Hof",
		"extra": "Höfe",
		"answer": ["udvar"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 613,
		"question": "die Zentrale",
		"extra": "Zentralen",
		"answer": ["központ"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 614,
		"question": "die Fläche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["terület"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 615,
		"question": "das Grundstück",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ingatlan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 616,
		"question": "die Insel",
		"extra": "Inseln",
		"answer": ["sziget"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 617,
		"question": "die Hauptstadt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["főváros"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 618,
		"question": "das Ferienhaus",
		"extra": "die Ferienhäuser",
		"answer": ["nyaraló ház"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 619,
		"question": "die Umgebung",
		"extra": "Umgebungen",
		"answer": ["környezet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 620,
		"question": "das Ausland",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["külföld"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 621,
		"question": "die Heimat",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["haza"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 622,
		"question": "das Innere",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["belső"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 623,
		"question": "der Standort",
		"extra": "Standorte",
		"answer": ["elhelyezkedés", "helyzet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 624,
		"question": "das Zentrum",
		"extra": "Zentren",
		"answer": ["központ"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 625,
		"question": "plötzlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hirtelen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 626,
		"question": "tatsächlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tulajdonképpen", "tényleg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 627,
		"question": "seltsam",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["különös", "furcsa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 628,
		"question": "allgemein",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["általában"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 629,
		"question": "zurückhaltend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szégyenlős"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 630,
		"question": "knapp",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szűkös"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 631,
		"question": "sinnvoll",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hasznos", "jelentőségteljes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 632,
		"question": "beliebt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["népszerű"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 633,
		"question": "wert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ér"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 634,
		"question": "echt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["igazán", "igazi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 635,
		"question": "ausgezeichnet",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kiváló"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 636,
		"question": "bereit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kész"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 637,
		"question": "verantwortlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["felelősségteljes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 638,
		"question": "sauer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["őrült"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 639,
		"question": "offen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyitott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 640,
		"question": "gemeinsam",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["együtt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 641,
		"question": "hart",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kemény"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 642,
		"question": "komish",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["különös", "furcsa"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 643,
		"question": "kaputt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["törött"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 644,
		"question": "fest",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szilárd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 1, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 645,
		"question": "zuständig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["felelős"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 646,
		"question": "weich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["puha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 647,
		"question": "hilfreich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["helpful"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 648,
		"question": "zufrieden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elégedett"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 649,
		"question": "begeistert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["izgatott"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 650,
		"question": "verfügbar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elérhető"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 651,
		"question": "notwendig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szükséges"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 652,
		"question": "selbstverständlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyértelmű", "magától értetődő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 653,
		"question": "eindeutig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tisztán"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 654,
		"question": "bekannt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ismert"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 655,
		"question": "sichtbar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["látható"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 656,
		"question": "abhängig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["függő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 657,
		"question": "unsichtbar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["láthatatlan"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 658,
		"question": "unabhängig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["független"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 659,
		"question": "nützlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hasznos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 660,
		"question": "möglich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lehetséges"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 661,
		"question": "praktisch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["praktikusm kényelmes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 662,
		"question": "unmöglich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lehetetlen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 663,
		"question": "persönlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["személyes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 664,
		"question": "verpflichtet",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elkötelezett"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 665,
		"question": "individuell",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyedi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 666,
		"question": "international",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nemzetközi"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 667,
		"question": "kostenlos",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ingyenes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 668,
		"question": "wahrscheinlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["valószínűleg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 669,
		"question": "deutlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tiszta", "érthető"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 670,
		"question": "voll",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["teli", "telt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 671,
		"question": "die Medikamente",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyógyszer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 672,
		"question": "der Patient",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["páciens"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 673,
		"question": "blute",
		"extra": "blutet",
		"answer": ["vérzik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 674,
		"question": "Pflaster",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sebtapasz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 675,
		"question": "Rollstuhl",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kerekes szék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 676,
		"question": "kaputt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["törött"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 677,
		"question": "krank",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["beteg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 678,
		"question": "die Praxis",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["praxis"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 679,
		"question": "der ärzt, die ärztin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["orvos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 680,
		"question": "die Untersuhung",
		"extra": "Untersuchungen",
		"answer": ["vizsgálat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 681,
		"question": "das Formular",
		"extra": "Formulare",
		"answer": ["forma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 682,
		"question": "die Krankheit",
		"extra": "Krankenheiten",
		"answer": ["betegség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 683,
		"question": "die Gesundheit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egészség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 684,
		"question": "die Medizin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyógyszer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 685,
		"question": "die Krankenversicherung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egészségbiztosítás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 686,
		"question": "der Krankenwagen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mentő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 687,
		"question": "das Krankenhaus",
		"extra": "Krankenhäuser",
		"answer": ["kórház"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 688,
		"question": "der Zahnarzt, die Zahnarztin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fogorvos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 689,
		"question": "das Opfer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["áldozat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 690,
		"question": "der Notfall",
		"extra": "Notfälle",
		"answer": ["vészhelyzet"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 691,
		"question": "der Unfall",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["baleset"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 692,
		"question": "die Klinik",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["klinika"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 693,
		"question": "die Therapie",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kezelés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 694,
		"question": "die Diät",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["diéta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 695,
		"question": "die Ernährung",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["táplálkozás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 696,
		"question": "der Alkohol",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["alkohol"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 697,
		"question": "singe",
		"extra": "singen",
		"answer": ["énekel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 698,
		"question": "weiß",
		"extra": "wissen",
		"answer": ["tud"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 699,
		"question": "halten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tart"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 700,
		"question": "arbeite",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dolgozik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 701,
		"question": "hoffe",
		"extra": "hoffen",
		"answer": ["remél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 702,
		"question": "nimme",
		"extra": "nehmen",
		"answer": ["elvesz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 703,
		"question": "könnt",
		"extra": "können",
		"answer": ["képes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 704,
		"question": "finde",
		"extra": "finden",
		"answer": ["talál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 705,
		"question": "suche",
		"extra": "suchen",
		"answer": ["keres"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 706,
		"question": "änderte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["változtat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 707,
		"question": "scheine",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fénylik", "tűnik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 708,
		"question": "warte",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 709,
		"question": "treffe",
		"extra": "treffen",
		"answer": ["találkozik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 710,
		"question": "stehe auf",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["feláll"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 711,
		"question": "neben",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mellett"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 712,
		"question": "glaube",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hisz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 713,
		"question": "lüge",
		"extra": "lügen",
		"answer": ["fekszik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 714,
		"question": "wen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kivel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 715,
		"question": "erkennen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["felismer"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 716,
		"question": "ersetzt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lecserél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 717,
		"question": "benutze",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["használ"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 718,
		"question": "schließen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bezár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 719,
		"question": "verpassen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hiányzik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 720,
		"question": "erweitern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kiterjeszt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 721,
		"question": "erlaubt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["enged"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 722,
		"question": "bestelle",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rendel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 723,
		"question": "übernimmt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["átvesz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 724,
		"question": "passiert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["történik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 725,
		"question": "danach",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["után"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 726,
		"question": "abonnieren",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["feliratkozik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 727,
		"question": "funktionert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["működik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 728,
		"question": "akzeptieren",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elfogad"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 729,
		"question": "spaziert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["sétál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 730,
		"question": "stiehlt",
		"extra": "stehlen",
		"answer": ["lop"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 731,
		"question": "prüfe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ellenőriz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 732,
		"question": "schaue",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["néz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 733,
		"question": "meinst",
		"extra": "meinen",
		"answer": ["ért"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 734,
		"question": "während",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["amíg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 735,
		"question": "sammeln",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyűjt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 736,
		"question": "steige",
		"extra": "steigen",
		"answer": ["feláll"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 737,
		"question": "fehlt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hiányzik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 738,
		"question": "monatlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["havonta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 739,
		"question": "seit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mióta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 740,
		"question": "Spargel",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["spárga"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 741,
		"question": "der Frühling",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tavasz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 742,
		"question": "der Sommer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 743,
		"question": "der Herbst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ősz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 744,
		"question": "der Winter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 745,
		"question": "der januar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["január"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 746,
		"question": "der februar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["február"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 747,
		"question": "der März",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["március"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 748,
		"question": "der April",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["április"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 749,
		"question": "der Mai",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["május"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 750,
		"question": "der Juni",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["június"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 751,
		"question": "der Juli",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["július"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 752,
		"question": "der August",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["augusztus"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 753,
		"question": "der September",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szeptember"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 754,
		"question": "der Oktober",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["október"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 755,
		"question": "der November",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["november"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 756,
		"question": "der Dezember",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["december"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 757,
		"question": "das Jahr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["év"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 758,
		"question": "der Monat",
		"extra": "Monate",
		"answer": ["hónap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 759,
		"question": "der Tage",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 1, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-5-30" }
	},
	{
		"id": 760,
		"question": "das Quartal",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["negyed"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 761,
		"question": "den dritten Oktober",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["október 3-a"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 762,
		"question": "kühl",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hűvös", "hideg"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 763,
		"question": "das Datum",
		"extra": "Daten",
		"answer": ["dátum"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 764,
		"question": "die Jahreszeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["évszak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 765,
		"question": "Kalender",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["naptár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 766,
		"question": "Weihnachten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Karácsony"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 767,
		"question": "die Phase",
		"extra": "Phasen",
		"answer": ["fázis"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 768,
		"question": "Einkaufszentrum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bevásárló központ"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 769,
		"question": "Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["Boldog születésnapot"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 770,
		"question": "feiere",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ünnepel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 771,
		"question": "also",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["így", "tehát"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 772,
		"question": "werde",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["válik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 773,
		"question": "das Geschenk",
		"extra": "Geschenke",
		"answer": ["ajándék"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 774,
		"question": "der Kuchen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["torta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 775,
		"question": "die Kertze",
		"extra": "Kerzen",
		"answer": ["gyertya"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 776,
		"question": "der Strand",
		"extra": "Strände",
		"answer": ["strand"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 777,
		"question": "der Tourist",
		"extra": "Touristen",
		"answer": ["túrista"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 778,
		"question": "das Jahrhundert",
		"extra": "Jahrhunderten",
		"answer": ["évszázad"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 779,
		"question": "denke",
		"extra": "denken",
		"answer": ["gondol", "hisz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 780,
		"question": "das Alter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 781,
		"question": "Schluss",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["elég"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 782,
		"question": "vorbei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["múlt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 783,
		"question": "der Moment",
		"extra": "Momente",
		"answer": ["pillanat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 784,
		"question": "der Termin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["időpont"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 785,
		"question": "steht fest",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["biztos", "rögzítve van"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 786,
		"question": "gestern",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tegnap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 787,
		"question": "heute",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ma"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 788,
		"question": "morgen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["holnap"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 789,
		"question": "der Nutzer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["felhasználó"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 790,
		"question": "der Verein",
		"extra": "Vereine",
		"answer": ["klub"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 791,
		"question": "die Verbindung",
		"extra": "Verbindungen",
		"answer": ["kapcsolat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 792,
		"question": "die Gemeinde",
		"extra": "Gemeinden",
		"answer": ["közösség"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 793,
		"question": "das Verhältnis",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kapcsolat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 794,
		"question": "der Öffentlichkeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyilvánosság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 795,
		"question": "Jugend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["fiatalság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 796,
		"question": "die Einwohner",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["lakos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 797,
		"question": "das Paar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["pár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 798,
		"question": "der Bürger",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["polgár"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 799,
		"question": "Man",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egy valaki"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 800,
		"question": "spät",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["késő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 801,
		"question": "die Nacht",
		"extra": "Nächte",
		"answer": ["éjjel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 802,
		"question": "Abend",
		"extra": "Abende",
		"answer": ["este"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 803,
		"question": "der Zeitraum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["időszak"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 804,
		"question": "früh",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["korán"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 805,
		"question": "die Stunde",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["óra"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 806,
		"question": "Sekunden",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["másodperc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 807,
		"question": "die Uhrzeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["idő"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 808,
		"question": "der Augenblick",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["pillanat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 809,
		"question": "die Uhr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["óra"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 810,
		"question": "Mitternacht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["éjfél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 811,
		"question": "der Zeitpunkt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["időpont"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 812,
		"question": "nachts",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["éjjel"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 813,
		"question": "sofort",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["azonnal"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 814,
		"question": "dauert",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["tart"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 815,
		"question": "die Dauer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["időtartam"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 816,
		"question": "gerade",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["most"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 817,
		"question": "etwa",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["körülbelül"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 818,
		"question": "damals",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["akkor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 819,
		"question": "fast",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["majdnem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 820,
		"question": "rede",
		"extra": "reden",
		"answer": ["beszél"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 821,
		"question": "vergesse",
		"extra": "vergessen",
		"answer": ["elfelejt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 822,
		"question": "löse",
		"extra": "lösen",
		"answer": ["megold"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 823,
		"question": "biete",
		"extra": "bieten",
		"answer": ["ajánl"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 824,
		"question": "merke",
		"extra": "merken",
		"answer": ["észrevesz", "rájön"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 825,
		"question": "schütze",
		"extra": "schützen",
		"answer": ["véd"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 826,
		"question": "berate",
		"extra": "beraten",
		"answer": ["tanácsot ad"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 827,
		"question": "die Angst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["félelem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 828,
		"question": "stolz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["büszke"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 829,
		"question": "böse",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["dühös"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 830,
		"question": "Lust",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kedv"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 831,
		"question": "Spaß",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["móka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 832,
		"question": "Wunsch",
		"extra": "Wünsche",
		"answer": ["kívánság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 833,
		"question": "die Freude",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["öröm"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 834,
		"question": "die Not",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nyomorúság"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 835,
		"question": "träume",
		"extra": "träumen",
		"answer": ["álmodik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 836,
		"question": "der Traum",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["álom"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 837,
		"question": "der Eindruck",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["benyomás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 838,
		"question": "Ernst",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["komoly"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 839,
		"question": "interessant",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["érdekes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 840,
		"question": "Gedanke",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gondolat"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 841,
		"question": "der Witz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vicc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 842,
		"question": "der Ruhe",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csend"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 843,
		"question": "langweilig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["unalmas"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 844,
		"question": "Humor",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["humor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 845,
		"question": "ehrlich",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bescsületes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 846,
		"question": "schlau",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["okos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 847,
		"question": "ärger",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["mérges"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 848,
		"question": "dumm",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["buta"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 849,
		"question": "witzig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["vicces"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 850,
		"question": "hasse",
		"extra": "hassen",
		"answer": ["utál"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 851,
		"question": "nett",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kedves"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 852,
		"question": "der Liebling",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kedvenc"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 853,
		"question": "Glück",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szerencse"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 854,
		"question": "das Verständnis",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["megértés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 855,
		"question": "gar nicht",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyáltalán nem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 856,
		"question": "schlimm",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["rossz"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 857,
		"question": "die Schuld",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["hibás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 858,
		"question": "tapfer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["bátor"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 859,
		"question": "lache",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["nevetés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 860,
		"question": "wunderbar",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csodás"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 861,
		"question": "hübsch",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["szép"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 862,
		"question": "wenige",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kevés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 863,
		"question": "manchmal",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["néha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 864,
		"question": "mehr",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["több"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 865,
		"question": "oft",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyakran"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 866,
		"question": "zahlreiche",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["számos"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 867,
		"question": "selten",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ritka"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 868,
		"question": "häufig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["gyakran"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 869,
		"question": "anderes",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["másik"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 870,
		"question": "bisschen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kevés"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 871,
		"question": "meist",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["legtöbb"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 872,
		"question": "keinerlei",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["egyik sem"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 873,
		"question": "ob",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ha"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 874,
		"question": "unbekannt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["ismeretlen"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 875,
		"question": "kann",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["képes"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 876,
		"question": "muss",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kell"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 877,
		"question": "soll",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["kellene"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 878,
		"question": "tun",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["csinálni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 879,
		"question": "kennenzulernen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": ["megismerni"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 880,
		"question": "entscheide",
		"extra": "entscheiden",
		"answer": ["eldönt"],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 881,
		"question": "aussage",
		"extra": "aussagen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 882,
		"question": "mitmache",
		"extra": "mitmachen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 883,
		"question": "registriere",
		"extra": "registrieren",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 884,
		"question": "darf",
		"extra": "dürfen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 885,
		"question": "teilnehme",
		"extra": "teilnehmen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 886,
		"question": "ersetze",
		"extra": "ersetzen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 887,
		"question": "betrachte",
		"extra": "betrachten",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 888,
		"question": "vorstelle",
		"extra": "vorstellen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 889,
		"question": "Schatz",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 890,
		"question": "Schauspieler",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 891,
		"question": "Sprachen",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 892,
		"question": "klug",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 893,
		"question": "der Fernseher",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 894,
		"question": "aufregend",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 895,
		"question": "das Kaufhaus",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 896,
		"question": "stressig",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 897,
		"question": "der Kellner",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 898,
		"question": "Die Vegetarierin",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 899,
		"question": "vegetarisches",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 900,
		"question": "Pommes",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 901,
		"question": "Schalter",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 902,
		"question": "Flugticket",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 903,
		"question": "Mathetest",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 904,
		"question": "dunkle",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 905,
		"question": "die Welt",
		"extra": "Welten",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 906,
		"question": "die Umwelt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 907,
		"question": "Waldeinsamkeit",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 908,
		"question": "der Schwarzwald",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 909,
		"question": "der Rhein",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 910,
		"question": "Fluss",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 911,
		"question": "See",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 912,
		"question": "die Welle",
		"extra": "Wellen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 913,
		"question": "Meer",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 914,
		"question": "Gras",
		"extra": "Gräser",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 915,
		"question": "Tierwelt",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 916,
		"question": "Wiese",
		"extra": "Wiesen",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 0, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 917,
		"question": "der Wald",
		"extra": "Wälder",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 0, "correct": 100, "incorrect": 100, "lastSeen": "2022-05-01" }
	},
	{
		"id": 918,
		"question": "Das All",
		"extra": "",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 1, "incorrect": 10, "lastSeen": "2022-04-21" }
	},
	{
		"id": 919,
		"question": "",
		"extra": "Flüsse",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1, "correct": 2, "incorrect": 4, "lastSeen": "2022-05-15" }
	},
	{
		"id": 920,
		"question": "der Bach",
		"extra": "Bäche",
		"answer": [],
		"tracker": { "seen": 1000, "correct": 10, "incorrect": 0, "lastSeen": "2022-05-19" }
	}
]
